( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
You've lost a lot of blood.
You'll need a few days' rest to recover.
I'll get you some blood-building medicine.
That way you'll heal faster.
And it'll be easier for you to leave.
You know medicine too?
Because I'm a patient myself.
The doctor said I have a serious illness.
I might not have long to live.
Three years.
Two years.
Or maybe tomorrow.
Doesn't that make you sad?
Not really.
At least I'm still alive right now.
I have lots of big brothers and sisters,
and uncles who care about me.
Actually, I'm grateful for my illness.
Because of it,
I can use what I've learned
to help more people.
Su Yang doesn't really dislike you.
It's just that at mealtimes,
he always has to grumble a bit.
If...
if you really have nowhere to go,
why not stay here?
I don't know how much longer I'll live.
If one day I'm gone,
no one will clean up for Su Yang anymore.
Someone he doesn't hate needs to look after him.
Otherwise,
he'll just get triggered again.
Su Yang's back!
This is for you.
In it goes.
Uncle Houzi, come eat!
Let me help you.
It's fine, I've got it.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Okay, okay.
Su Yang promised not to kill randomly.
Sit down.
Sit.
Oh right,
I forgot you can't eat
anything greasy or salty right now.
I made you some porridge for lunch.
Here.
It shouldn't be too hot.
Perfect.
Still warm.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm full.
I'm apologizing on Su Yang's behalf.
He may act crazy sometimes,
but everything he does
has a reason behind it.
He doesn't truly mean to harm people.
I don't expect you to forgive him,
but if one day in the future,
you see Su Yang lying in a pool of blood,
barely breathing,
please just don't deliver the final blow.
Su Yang has said
that day will come for him eventually.
Let's eat.
From this moment on,
we're establishing the Lingxiao
Network Surveillance Division.
Everyone's working overtime.
Track online forum comments 24/7.
Maintain full monitoring and screening.
Keep a tight watch on Black Street.
In three days,
I want to see on my desk
a complete list
containing 80 percent
of Shanhai City's Blessed Ones.
Can you do it?
Alright, meeting adjourned.
The reason I came here today
is to announce something to all of you.
Our Shanhai City
will form a squad of Blessed Ones.
The name
is Lingxiao.
In mythology,
Lingxiao represents the heavenly court above.
And now,
in the name of Lingxiao,
we fulfill our duty to protect,
guarding every home in Shanhai City.
Even if
it costs us our lives.
Are you confident?
Yes!
Limpy hates being disturbed during his nap.
Scared?
Me? Scared?
Tongtong's been taken.
What about Su Yang?
Still don't know.
It was that guy Houzi
who used his last breath to warn us.
What the hell is he thinking this time?
Based on what the Marketing Department
has compiled so far,
the immortals seem to randomly select
mortals with similar personalities
to bestow blessings upon.
The Blessed can borrow the immortals' power.
Randomly?
Yes, with no discernible pattern.
And so far,
the Blessed Ones
can only borrow very limited abilities.
Mostly strength, speed,
just basic attribute boosts.
According to algorithmic analysis,
this may be because the Blessed Ones
aren't strong enough yet.
As their physical strength improves,
they may access more techniques.
Starting now,
spare no expense.
Hire the Blessed Ones
to keep studying immortal blessings
for deeper analysis.
Money is no object.
Understood.
Youngest Blessed One emerges:
a ten-year-old boy,
registered on Chunfeng Rd by his parents.
Linhai Group's CEO reveals he's a Blessed One.
In today's dating market,
Blessed Ones are in the highest demand.
Stop.
Stop, stop.
The point is,
among all these Blessed Ones,
is there anyone exceptionally powerful?
Yes.
Who?
Xu Siguo.
Who's Xu Siguo?
Don't know.
I don't have any info on him.
Then go find some!
Go, hurry up!
Fast, fast, fast!
I really do like that girl.
Just follow your own heart.
Something big happened!
Hurry, go deliver the news!
Got it!
Sangou.
Five minutes.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
You know what I want to ask, right?
No, I...
I'm in a bad mood right now.
I'd appreciate your cooperation.
I really don't know what you mean.
I told you,
I'm in a bad mood.
And I'm in a hurry.
Tongtong.
Tongtong left Black Street this morning.
She was kidnapped on her way back.
By the time we got there, they were gone.
After checking surveillance footage,
we found they're all unregistered citizens.
Right now,
the only lead we have
is that they headed west.
The rest...
The rest is still under investigation.
Thank you.
They went west.
That's all we know.
West.
Yes.
That lead is way too vague.
Tongtong.
Where's Tongtong? Shut up.
Where is Tongtong?
From now on,
if you want to save Tongtong, shut your mouth.
Okay.
Knowing the Liu family's style,
they won't take this matter seriously.
Let's kill our way west.
One person every mile.
Until they give us answers.
Let me handle this.
Qian.
Kun.
Zhen.
Xun.
Kan.
Li.
Gen.
Dui.
Fuxi's Eight Trigrams.
Ill omen. Southwest.
I knew you were blessed, old man.
If Tongtong hadn't been taken,
how much longer would you have hidden it?
I'm borrowing your car.
Pick it up at this time tomorrow.
Someone who can drive, get up here.
If you want to save Tongtong, sit in the back.
Okay.
Bunch of old geezers.
Those guys
have left Black Street.
It's time to meet the people of Black Street.
In case they really cause trouble,
I needed data on Shanhai's Blessed Ones.
Have you finished it?
Who's the strongest?
Su Yang.
Besides him?
Xu Siguo.
I've heard you mention him.
Call him over.
He'll come with me on the operation.
Good chance to see his strength.
Who has contacts for other Black Street people?
Have someone stake out the clinic.
If that madman shows up,
make him get his ass over here ASAP.
If Tongtong dies,
he goes down with her.
Buried with her.
But we can't beat him.
Shut up.
Okay.
There's a car tailing us.
Take it easy.
Liu family men.
Introduce yourselves.
Shanhai City.
Liu family.
Liu Chengfeng.
Once the seed sprouts,
the cleaner's condition will be contained.
Madman, Limpy has news.
I need a favor.
Help my friend
take a bath.
Okay.
Thank you.
Houzi
The sky...
seems to have gotten darker.
I know
you are all furious.
But this is the Liu family's negligence.
I hope you will give us a chance
to handle this matter ourselves.
I promise
to return her safely to Black Street.
What do you say?
Black Street handles its own affairs.
No need to trouble the Liu family.
So there's no room for negotiation?
Well, in that case,
I still hope all of you
won't make this too ugly.
After all, the Liu family
still has its dignity to uphold.
When immortals comply, praises are sung.
When they defy, what can they do to me?
Yang Jian,
manifest!
What's he doing?
He's going to fight.
Why fight?
Because you said
the Liu family needs its dignity too.
Nice.
He's going to fight you.
Fight me?
So weak.
I'd like to ask,
is he really, as of now,
the strongest Blessed One in Shanhai?
He was very eager when he signed up.
Just a bit shy.
Then how can someone like him
be captain of Lingxiao?
I still can't let this go.
I want to confirm one last time.
Is there anyone stronger than him?
Okay, okay, okay.
Come back.
Come back, come back, come back.
Come on, come on.
I... I can still do it.
I know, I know, I know.
But haven't you noticed
the guy over there is stronger than us?
Um,
sorry about this.
Sorry to waste everyone's time.
Go do whatever you were doing.
Don't mind us at all.
We're all a bit messed up in the head.
I'll do it.
Idiot.
You have to pull it open.
Tongtong!
This Limpy moves pretty fast.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I'm commandeering your carriage.
Tongtong!
You killed Tongtong!
I'll fight you to the death!